The Reese Family Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- Graphic Materials, 1850 - 1984; 8; Boxes: 70 - 76 Folders: 1 - 54, 1 - 65, 1 - 81, 1- 46, 1 - 35, 1 - 11, 1 - 17
  - The Reese Family, 1953 - 1984; 8.2; About X linear feet Boxes: 70 - 71 Folders: 3 - 54, 1 - 65
    - Frances Stevens Reese, 8.2.2; Box: 70 Folders: 15 - 29
      - Twelve photos of Frances Reese with Marist President Dennis Murray among others at Val-Kill, the Eleanor Roosevelt National Historic Site, 1996 October (Folder 24, Box 70)
      - Thirteen photos of Frances Reese with Marist President Dennis Murray among others at Val-Kill, the Eleanor Roosevelt National Historic Site, 1996 October (Folder 25, Box 70)
      - Eleven paper photos of Frances Reese and others at public event at Obercreek, undated (Folder 26, Box 70)
      - Large photo of Frances Reese with man, undated (Folder 27, Box 70)
      - Photo of Frances Reese with man, undated (Folder 28, Box 70)
      - Frances Reese holding photo of The Right Reverend Richard F. Grein, undated (Folder 29, Box 70)
    - Ancestors of Willis L.M. Reese, 8.2.3; Box: 70 Folders: 30 - 37
      - Maria Reese Clarkson - Tante Ria, undated (Folder 30, Box 70)
      - William Willis Reese (father of Willis L.M. Reese), undated (Folder 31, Box 70)
      - William Willis Reese (father of Willis L.M. Reese), undated (Folder 32, Box 70)
      - William Henry Reese, 1836-1916, married Mary Augusta Willis; or William Henry Willis, 1842-1918, married Adele Marie Satterlee, undated (Folder 33, Box 70)
      - William Henry Reese, 1836-1916, married Mary Augusta Willis; or William Henry Willis, 1842-1918, married Adele Marie Satterlee, undated (Folder 34, Box 70)
      - Peggy Reese, 3 years old, daughter of John H. Reese, undated (Folder 35, Box 70)
      - W. H. Reese, undated (Folder 36, Box 70)
      - Elizabeth Irving [?] Reese, aged 7 months, Barrows Boston written on front, 1901 November (Folder 37, Box 70)
    - Possible ancestors, 8.2.4; Boxes: 70 Folders: 38 - 54
      - Folder that contained files 40-51 and 1-4 in next box, undated (Folder 38, Box 70)
      - Amy Brardman [?], undated (Folder 39, Box 70)
      - Amy Brardman [?], undated (Folder 40, Box 70)
      - Rose Perkin, undated (Folder 41, Box 70)
      - Rose Perkin, undated (Folder 42, Box 70)
      - Rose Perkin, undated (Folder 43, Box 70)
      - Rose Perkin, undated (Folder 44, Box 70)
      - Alice Perkin, undated (Folder 45, Box 70)
      - Alice Perkin, undated (Folder 46, Box 70)
      - Marie Banks, undated (Folder 47, Box 70)
      - Marie Banks, undated (Folder 48, Box 70)
      - Lyndia “Lily” Framer Folston [?], undated (Folder 49, Box 70)
      - Lyndia “Lily” Framer Folston [?], undated (Folder 50, Box 70)
      - Unknown Man, undated (Folder 51, Box 70)
      - Same Unknown Woman, undated (Folder 52, Box 70)
      - Same Unknown Woman, undated (Folder 53, Box 70)
      - Same Unknown Woman, undated (Folder 54, Box 70)
    - Children, 8.2.5; Boxes: 71 Folders: 1 - 27
      - Envelope, labeled George and Alec Reese, contained files 1-11, undated (Folder 1, Box 71)
      - Unknown family photo, undated (Folder 2, Box 71)
      - Unknown family photo, baseball game, undated (Folder 3, Box 71)
      - Photo on board R.M.S. Queen Elizabeth, Frances Reese with two children, most likely Frances Gallatin Reese and John Rathbone Reese, undated (Folder 4, Box 71)
      - Alec and George (George Bliss Reese holding Alexander Stevens Reese), 1953 (Folder 5, Box 71)
      - Alec and George (George Bliss Reese holding Alexander Stevens Reese), 1953 (Folder 6, Box 71)
      - Alec (Alexander Stevens Reese), 1953 (Folder 7, Box 71)
      - Alec (Alexander Stevens Reese), 1953 (Folder 8, Box 71)
      - Alec (Alexander Stevens Reese), 1953 (Folder 9, Box 71)
      - Alec (Alexander Stevens Reese), 1953 (Folder 10, Box 71)
      - Alec (Alexander Stevens Reese), 1953 (Folder 11, Box 71)
      - George and Alex Reese (George Bliss Reese and Alexander Stevens Reese), 1953-1954 (Folder 12, Box 71)
      - George (Bliss) Reese, circa 1950 (Folder 13, Box 71)
      - Saudro, undated (Folder 14, Box 71)
      - Large photo of trees, undated (Folder 15, Box 71)
      - Large photo of dog, undated (Folder 16, Box 71)
      - Millbrook School - Large photo, undated (Folder 17, Box 71)
      - Saudro, undated (Folder 18, Box 71)
      - George B. Reese, undated (Folder 19, Box 71)
      - John Rathbone Reese [?], undated (Folder 20, Box 71)
      - Reese boys, likely John and George, undated (Folder 21, Box 71)
      - Two boys playing tennis, likely either John or George, undated (Folder 22, Box 71)
      - Lawrence School, undated (Folder 23, Box 71)
      - Lawrence School baseball team, undated (Folder 24, Box 71)
      - Lawrence School Band, Alec Reese, second from left with clarinet, undated (Folder 25, Box 71)
      - Gusta Reese by E. Ballantine (Augusta Bliss Reese, daughter of John Rathbone Reese), circa 1975 (Folder 26, Box 71)
      - Vivi Reese by E. Ballantine (Victoria Reese, daughter of John Rathbone Reese), circa 1975 (Folder 27, Box 71)
    - On Board the Trimaran with the Fred Osborns and more, 1971; 8.2.6; Box: 71 Folders: 28 - 48
      - On Board the Trimaran with the Fred Osborns; John Reese and Vivi, October 1971 (Folder 28, Box 71)
      - Augusta Reese, October 1971 (Folder 29, Box 71)
      - Augusta Reese, October 1971 (Folder 30, Box 71)
      - Hudson - near Newburgh Bay, October 1971 (Folder 31, Box 71)
      - Hudson River, October 1971 (Folder 32, Box 71)
      - Hudson - near Newburgh Bay, October 1971 (Folder 33, Box 71)
      - Gorge - Hudson River, October 1971 (Folder 34, Box 71)
      - Hudson Gorge, October 1971 (Folder 35, Box 71)
      - Hudson Gorge, October 1971 (Folder 36, Box 71)
      - Gorge - Hudson River, October 1971 (Folder 37, Box 71)
      - Franny Oliveri [?] with Chess and Sandro, October 1971 (Folder 38, Box 71)
      - West Point, October 1971 (Folder 39, Box 71)
      - John Reese, Franny Orivieri [?], October 1971 (Folder 40, Box 71)
      - Hudson Gorge, October 1971 (Folder 41, Box 71)
      - Cold Spring, October 1971 (Folder 42, Box 71)
      - Obercreek Pond, October 1971 (Folder 43, Box 71)
      - Crosier from Montclair House, October 1971 (Folder 44, Box 71)
      - Obercreek Pond and “Gobea”, 1971 (Folder 45, Box 71)
      - Pond Grading - Obercreek, October 1971 (Folder 46, Box 71)
      - Danskammer, April 1971 (Folder 47, Box 71)
      - Film negatives from On Board the Trimaran with the Fred Osborns and more, October 1971 (Folder 48, Box 71)
    - Miscellany, 8.2.7; Box: 71 Folders: 49 - 65
      - Postcard from the Winnisook Club, Oliverea, Ulster County, N.Y., undated (Folder 49, Box 71)
      - Postcard from the Winnisook Club, Oliverea, Ulster County, N.Y., undated (Folder 50, Box 71)
      - Postcard from the Winnisook Club, Oliverea, Ulster County, N.Y., undated (Folder 51, Box 71)
      - Large photograph of Franklin Delano Roosevelt at some sort of ceremony, undated (Folder 52, Box 71)
      - Photograph in cloth frame of child next to Balto statue in Central Park, New York City, found in Frances Reese Papers, Notebooks and bundled works, Documents found in Notebook 3, 1.6.5.3.12.2, undated (Folder 53, Box 71)
      - Irene Devries outside Pan American plane, Verso: To Fran and Willis, From Irene Haven [?], April 1973 (Folder 54, Box 71)
      - Three unknown children in wheelbarrow, with note found in Frances Reese Papers, 1.6.1.7.4, undated (Folder 55, Box 71)
      - Merry Christmas from Upper Brandon, VA, home of cousin Mizier and Ottoway Byrd, undated (Folder 56, Box 71)
      - Merry Christmas, to Bill, from Lucy and Ed bullier[?], undated (Folder 57, Box 71)
      - Unknown man on sidewalk, undated (Folder 58, Box 71)
      - Unknown woman in garden path, undated (Folder 59, Box 71)
      - Three photos of unknown woman in chair, undated (Folder 60, Box 71)
      - Unknown woman in hospital bed, undated (Folder 61, Box 71)
      - Edward Robertson - found in Frame 1, undated (Folder 62, Box 71)
      - Frame 1, undated (Folder 63, Box 71)
      - Anna Robertson, wife of Edward Robertson - found in Frame 2, undated (Folder 64, Box 71)
      - Frame 2, undated (Folder 65, Box 71)
  - 8.3: The Stevens Family, 1860 - 1925; 8.3; Boxes: 71 - 72 Folders: 66 - 71, 1 - 49
    - Henry Hewgill Stevens - tintype, circa 1860s (Folder 66, Box 71)
    - Francis Kerby Stevens - cabinet card, circa 1878 (Folder 67, Box 71)
    - Francis Kerby Stevens - cabinet card [four copies], May 1880 (Folder 68, Box 71)
    - Francis Kerby Stevens - cabinet card, circa 1885 (Folder 69, Box 71)
    - Francis Kerby Stevens - cabinet card, circa 1886 (Folder 70, Box 71)
    - Francis Kerby Stevens - cabinet card, circa 1886 (Folder 71, Box 71)
    - Francis Kerby Stevens - cabinet card, circa 1893 (Folder 1, Box 72)
    - Francis Kerby Stevens - cabinet card, circa 1893 (Folder 2, Box 72)
    - Francis Kerby Stevens - cabinet card, circa 1893 (Folder 3, Box 72)
    - Francis Kerby Stevens - cabinet card, 1897 (Folder 4, Box 72)
    - Francis Kerby Stevens - cabinet card, circa 1889 (Folder 5, Box 72)
    - Francis Kerby Stevens on “Ajax” (horse), 11/2, circa 1905 (Folder 6, Box 72)
    - Portrait of Francis Kerby Stevens, circa 1902 (Folder 7, Box 72)
    - Portrait of Francis Kerby Stevens, circa 1907 (Folder 8, Box 72)
    - Portrait of Francis Kerby Stevens, circa 1907 (Folder 9, Box 72)
    - Portrait of Francis Kerby Stevens, circa 1920s (Folder 10, Box 72)
    - 130 Broadway, Lawrence, Long Island, home of Alexander Henry Stevens and his daughter Mary Otis Stevens, Elizabeth (Shaw) Oliver Stevens in Garden, Mary Otis Stevens and Aunt Fanny(?) [4 photos], undated (Folder 11, Box 72)
    - Two women with broom, man sitting in chair could be Alexander Henry Stevens[?], man in background, undated (Folder 12, Box 72)
    - Two men standing, man in chair could be Alexander Henry Stevens [?], undated (Folder 13, Box 72)
    - Grounds of large house, could be in Lawrence, Long Island or likely Gladstone, New Jersey, undated (Folder 14, Box 72)
    - Snow covered road with thin tracks, undated (Folder 15, Box 72)
    - Boy playing with dogs outside house, could be in Lawrence, Long Island or Gladstone, New Jersey, undated (Folder 16, Box 72)
    - Group of men and women picnicking in the grass, undated (Folder 17, Box 72)
    - Envelope that contained the photos in files 19-32, undated (Folder 18, Box 72)
    - Elizabeth Shaw Stevens, Gladstone, New Jersey, circa 1911 (Folder 19, Box 72)
    - Elizabeth Shaw Stevens, Gladstone, New Jersey, circa 1911 (Folder 20, Box 72)
    - Elizabeth Shaw Stevens, outside in pen, Gladstone, New Jersey, circa 1911 (Folder 21, Box 72)
    - Elizabeth Shaw Stevens, outside in pen with woman, Gladstone, New Jersey, circa 1911 (Folder 22, Box 72)
    - Either Elizabeth Shaw Stevens or Frances Gallatin Stevens as child, undated (Folder 23, Box 72)
    - Francis Kerby Stevens holding Elizabeth Shaw Stevens at 130 Broadway, Lawrence, Long Island, 1910 May (Folder 24, Box 72)
    - Child with Calf, likely Elizabeth Shaw Stevens at Gladstone, New Jersey, undated (Folder 25, Box 72)
    - Child with Calf, likely Elizabeth Shaw Stevens at Gladstone, New Jersey, undated (Folder 26, Box 72)
    - Child in doorway, undated (Folder 27, Box 72)
    - Child in doorway, undated (Folder 28, Box 72)
    - Child with Calf, likely Elizabeth Shaw Stevens at Gladstone, New Jersey, undated (Folder 29, Box 72)
    - Child crawling in grass, undated (Folder 30, Box 72)
    - Child standing in grass, undated (Folder 31, Box 72)
    - Envelope that contained the photos in files 34-42, undated (Folder 32, Box 72)
    - Negative photo of cattle, likely Gladstone, New Jersey, undated (Folder 33, Box 72)
    - Negative photo of cattle, likely Gladstone, New Jersey, undated (Folder 34, Box 72)
    - Negative photo of cattle, likely Gladstone, New Jersey, undated (Folder 35, Box 72)
    - Negative photo of cattle, likely Gladstone, New Jersey, undated (Folder 36, Box 72)
    - Negative photo of cattle, likely Gladstone, New Jersey, undated (Folder 37, Box 72)
    - Negative photo of cattle, likely Gladstone, New Jersey, undated (Folder 38, Box 72)
    - Negative photo of cattle, likely Gladstone, New Jersey, undated (Folder 39, Box 72)
    - Negative photo of cattle, likely Gladstone, New Jersey, undated (Folder 40, Box 72)
    - Negative photo of cattle, likely Gladstone, New Jersey, undated (Folder 41, Box 72)
    - Negative photo of cattle, likely Gladstone, New Jersey, undated (Folder 42, Box 72)
    - Small photograph of Elizabeth Shaw Oliver - found in Frame 3, circa 1895 (Folder 43, Box 72)
    - Frame 3, undated (Folder 44, Box 72)
    - Small photograph of Francis Kerby Stevens - found in Frame 4, circa 1900 (Folder 45, Box 72)
    - Frame 4, undated (Folder 46, Box 72)
    - Cabinet card of unknown woman, undated (Folder 47, Box 72)
    - Found with Francis Kerby Stevens Papers, 4.9.1.53.2 correspondence, [Seven wartime letters to Francis Kerby Stevens from his niece, Mary Swan on the Isle of Wight, England and letter from her landlord [?]] Verso: Taken on the Ryde War Savings Parade, September 11th, 1941, a colour party of scouts with their [illegible] - District Commissioner (cubs) M.S. [Mary Swan], 1941 September 11 (Folder 48, Box 72)
    - Three paintings of Mary Otis Stevens as a child, undated (Folder 49, Box 72)
  - The Davie Family, 8.4; Box: 72 Folders: 50 - 61
    - Photograph labeled Hollywood 1944, with May Davie and Dianne Durben (Folder 50, Box 72)
    - Contact sheet, eleven photographs of May Davie at Desk, undated (Folder 51, Box 72)
    - Contact sheet, twelve photographs of May Davie in dress on couch, undated (Folder 52, Box 72)
    - Contact sheet, eleven photographs of May Davie in dress on couch, undated (Folder 53, Box 72)
    - Portrait of May Davie, undated (Folder 54, Box 72)
    - Photograph of May Davie, 1948 (Folder 55, Box 72)
    - Photograph of May Davie, 6 copies, undated (Folder 56, Box 72)
    - Portrait of May Davie, undated (Folder 57, Box 72)
    - Photograph of May Davie holding rifle, standing over dead deer, undated (Folder 58, Box 72)
    - Cabinet card of Adolf Ladenberg, father of May Davie, undated (Folder 59, Box 72)
    - Portrait of man in United States military uniform written: Happy [Landings?] to May and Preston, [illegible] Haynes; verso: to May Davie from Haynes, undated (Folder 60, Box 72)
    - Large photograph of May Davie in dress on couch, undated (Folder 61, Box 72)
  - The Rathbone Family, 1850 - 1927; 8.5; Box: 72 Folders: 62 - 81
    - Cabinet card of Mary Allen Baker, wife of John Finley Rathbone, undated (Folder 62, Box 72)
    - Cabinet card of Alice Rathbone, Mrs. Archibald Murray, Great Aunt of Frances Stevens Reese, undated (Folder 63, Box 72)
    - Cabinet card of Grace Rathbone Shaw, undated (Folder 64, Box 72)
    - Cabinet card of Grace Rathbone Shaw, undated (Folder 65, Box 72)
    - Carte de visite of Marion Rathbone, circa 1850s (Folder 66, Box 72)
    - Carte de visite of Marion and Lucy Rathbone as children, circa 1850s (Folder 67, Box 72)
    - Carte de visite of Marion and Parker [Lucy?] Rathbone, circa 1850s (Folder 68, Box 72)
    - Carte de visite of Marion Rathbone, circa 1850s (Folder 69, Box 72)
    - Cabinet card of Jack Rathbone in Civil War era uniform, undated (Folder 70, Box 72)
    - Cabinet card of unknown man in Civil War era uniform, undated (Folder 71, Box 72)
    - Cabinet card of John Finley Rathbone, undated (Folder 72, Box 72)
    - Photograph of John Finley Rathbone with dogs, undated (Folder 73, Box 72)
    - Photograph of two men and one woman sitting near pavilion; Lennox House, home of John Rathbone, 1890 July (Folder 74, Box 72)
    - Cabinet card of Edward Bowditch; Verso: (Oliver connection) [cousin of Marion Rathbone Oliver], undated (Folder 75, Box 72)
    - Photograph of woman holding baby, undated (Folder 76, Box 72)
    - Photograph of Marion Rathbone Oliver with dog; Written: Doctor Barker and Marion, 1927 January (Folder 77, Box 72)
    - Portrait of John Finley Rathbone, two copies; Verso: General John Rathbone of Albany, Great Grandfather of F.S. Reese, undated (Folder 78, Box 72)
    - Two paper frames that contained portraits of John Finley Rathbone, undated (Folder 79, Box 72)
    - Negative of John Finley Rathbone portrait with original envelope, undated (Folder 80, Box 72)
    - Photographs found with letter to Elizabeth Oliver Stevens (Bessie) in 6.1.58.17, 1918 October (Folder 81, Box 72)
  - The Oliver Family, 1873 - 1930; 8.6; Boxes: 73 - 76 Folders: 1 - 46, 1 - 35, 1 - 11, 1 - 17
    - Cabinet Card of Marion Rathbone Oliver, undated (Folder 1, Box 73)
    - Cabinet Card of Marion Rathbone Oliver, undated (Folder 2, Box 73)
    - Cabinet Card of Marion Rathbone Oliver, Verso: Mrs. R.S. Oliver my grandmother (F.S. Reese), undated (Folder 3, Box 73)
    - Cabinet Card of eleven people sitting in parlor, includes Marion Rathbone Oliver, undated (Folder 4, Box 73)
    - Photograph of Robert Shaw Oliver, circa 1870 (Folder 5, Box 73)
    - Photograph of Robert Shaw Oliver, U.S. Army, 1969 (Folder 6, Box 73)
    - Cabinet Card of Robert Shaw Oliver as Colonel, undated (Folder 7, Box 73)
    - Cabinet Card of Robert Shaw Oliver seated in dress uniform, undated (Folder 8, Box 73)
    - Cabinet Card of Robert Shaw Oliver, undated (Folder 9, Box 73)
    - Mounted photograph of Robert Shaw Oliver, undated (Folder 10, Box 73)
    - Two cabinet cards of Robert Shaw Oliver posing with cape and crown, undated (Folder 11, Box 73)
    - Cabinet Card of Robert Shaw Oliver, Verso: Robert Shaw Oliver The Chancellor in Iolonthe, undated (Folder 12, Box 73)
    - Photograph of the Olivers and Bowditches, Verso: (1st cousins) Elizabeth Oliver, John Rathbone Oliver, Cora Oliver?, Marion Oliver?, Neddy Bowditch, circa 1887 (Folder 13, Box 73)
    - Cabinet Card of Elizabeth Shaw Oliver holding dog (Fetch) with other children on hammock, 1885 September (Folder 14, Box 73)
    - Mounted photograph [faded] of John Finley Rathbone playing with dog (Fetch) at Lennox, the dog and home of Elizabeth Shaw Oliver, 1886 (Folder 15, Box 73)
    - Large photograph of Marion Choate in wedding dress, she married Charles Harding, undated (Folder 16, Box 73)
    - Cabinet Card of Elizabeth Shaw Oliver and Robert Shaw Oliver on lake bank with canoe [Lake George?], undated (Folder 17, Box 73)
    - Cabinet Card of a group of people on log porch near lake, undated (Folder 18, Box 73)
    - Photograph of baby in playpen outside, woman cut off, undated (Folder 19, Box 73)
    - Photograph labeled Elizabeth and Frances Stevens, [Elizabeth Shaw Stevens], undated (Folder 20, Box 73)
    - Cabinet card of Elizabeth Shaw Oliver, circa 1880 (Folder 21, Box 73)
    - Boston, a group of women around Elizabeth Shaw Oliver in costume, Verso: Miss Oliver, with the good wishes of your photographer and fellow-student Bertha G. Davidson, Seymour Street, Boston Massachusetts, Life-class, 1894 April 30 (Folder 22, Box 73)
    - Cabinet card of snowshoe club, group of women in Albany, 1888 (Folder 23, Box 73)
    - Cabinet card of snowshoe club, group of women in Albany Verso: Taken by Robert Shaw Oliver, 1= B. Pruyn, 2= M. Lard, 3= G. Parker, 4= L. Parker, 5= H. Parning, 6= C. Oliver, 7= J. Wasson, 8= G. Lard, 9= E. Oliver [Elizabeth], 10= A. Battershall, 1888 (Folder 24, Box 73)
    - Cabinet Card of Elizabeth Shaw in Costume, 1894 (Folder 25, Box 73)
    - “Bertie” Pruyn, Elizabeth Oliver’s best friend, Albany, Verso: Hibertha L. Pruyn, ages 13, 1887 February (Folder 26, Box 73)
    - Mounted photo of Fetch - Elizabeth Oliver’s dog [different dog all other Fetchs are same dog], undated (Folder 27, Box 73)
    - Cabinet card of Fetch - Elizabeth Shaw Oliver’s dog, undated (Folder 28, Box 73)
    - Photograph of a group of girls, labeled: Pointe a Pic P.Q. Canada - Robert Shaw Oliver HWSC, undated (Folder 29, Box 73)
    - Close up of group of girls, labeled: Marion Oliver with Choate and other children, Pointe a Pic, Canada, undated (Folder 30, Box 73)
    - Photograph of St. Lawrence River at Point a Pic, Quebec, undated (Folder 31, Box 73)
    - Photograph of driveway with stonewall, undated (Folder 32, Box 73)
    - Large photograph of man pushing woman on canoe through wilderness, undated (Folder 33, Box 73)
    - Cabinet card of Robert Shaw Oliver and Elizabeth Shaw Oliver canoeing on Lake George, 1891 (Folder 34, Box 73)
    - Cabinet card of Elizabeth Shaw Oliver and John Rathbone Oliver canoeing on Lake George, 1891 (Folder 35, Box 73)
    - Cabinet card of Robert Shaw Oliver and John Rathbone Oliver canoeing on Lake George, 1891 (Folder 36, Box 73)
    - Group of people on porch steps [Murray Bay/Point a Pic] includes Elizabeth Shaw Oliver, undated (Folder 37, Box 73)
    - Group of people on porch steps [Murray Bay/Point a Pic] includes Elizabeth Shaw Oliver, Mrs. Ottway Byrd (cousin Mizie Bowditch) and President Taft?, undated (Folder 38, Box 73)
    - Mounted photograph of two women walking away, undated (Folder 39, Box 73)
    - Mounted photograph of group of people waving in woods, undated (Folder 40, Box 73)
    - Mounted photograph of a group of people by canoes, including Theodore Roosevelt?, undated (Folder 41, Box 73)
    - Group of people on porch steps [Murray Bay/Point a Pic] includes Elizabeth Shaw Oliver and Theodore Roosevelt, undated (Folder 42, Box 73)
    - Mounted photograph of a group of people cooking outside, includes Elizabeth Shaw Oliver, undated (Folder 43, Box 73)
    - Mounted photograph of people with fishing poles, includes Elizabeth Shaw Oliver, undated (Folder 44, Box 73)
    - Two proportraits of Elizabeth Shaw Oliver, undated (Folder 45, Box 73)
    - Mounted photographs of Elizabeth Shaw Oliver and Francis Kerby Stevens, among others, riding horses in Gladstone, N.J. - three photographs, undated (Folder 46, Box 73)
    - Photograph of 130 Broadway, Lawrence, Long Island - home of Alexander Henry Stevens, undated (Folder 1, Box 74)
    - Photograph of Francis Kerby Stevens and “Bessie,” a cow, undated (Folder 2, Box 74)
    - Photograph of “Bessie,” the cow, undated (Folder 3, Box 74)
    - Photograph labeled: Guernsey Breeders Association, Mr. Knowlton, Verso: Re: Gladstone Farms N.J., circa 1922 (Folder 4, Box 74)
    - Photograph of children with calf, includes Elizabeth Shaw Stevens and Frances Gallatin Stevens, Verso: Harold Smith (at head of calf) winner of prize for [illegible] best score in [illegible], N.J. Guernsey Breeders 1st annual picnic, Stonehouse farm, Gladstone, N.J., circa 1922 (Folder 5, Box 74)
    - Photograph of event of the Guernsey Breeders Association, circa 1922 (Folder 6, Box 74)
    - Photograph of milk tasting event of the Guernsey Breeders Association, includes Francis Kerby Stevens and Elizabeth Oliver Stevens, circa 1922 (Folder 7, Box 74)
    - Photograph of group of people at Guernsey Breeders Association, includes Mr. and Mrs. Francis Kerby Stevens, circa 1922 (Folder 8, Box 74)
    - Photograph of event of the Guernsey Breeders Association, circa 1922 (Folder 9, Box 74)
    - Photograph of event of the Guernsey Breeders Association, cattle lined up for judging, circa 1922 (Folder 10, Box 74)
    - Photograph of cattle, Verso: Stonehouse Farm, Guernsey Bull, Morris County Fair, N.J. - Mrs. F.K. Stevens, Gladstone, NJ; 1st prize Greater Interstate bull 2-3 1920; 2nd prize Greater Interstate bull aged 1921; 1st with herd [illegible] of Stonehouse, Pandora, [illegible], circa 1922 (Folder 11, Box 74)